[ti:Liar Liar (Avicii By Avicii)]
[ar:Avicii]
[al:True: Avicii By Avicii]

[00:00.98]Liar Liar (Avicii By Avicii) - Avicii
[01:23.01]Follow you to dust
[01:25.60][01:32.81][01:37.41][01:40.66][01:46.52][01:55.74][02:10.69][02:18.21][02:36.41]
[01:26.39]Leaving footprints on the
[01:28.86]clouds as we're walking home
[01:30.83]Iron hearts all turn to rust
[01:34.33]By tears and the days on a diamond street
[01:38.22]Chasing shadows
[01:41.87]living dreams that don't exist
[01:45.72]Anymore
[01:49.45]We need to find a way
[01:52.32][02:02.93]Well, we are who we are,
[01:54.38][02:08.82]and we're all going under
[01:59.54][02:14.53]When the past with the last
[02:01.41][02:16.28]and will last until under
[02:35.21]Liar, liar!
