[ti:Lay Me Down (Avicii By Avicii)]
[ar:Avicii]
[al:True: Avicii By Avicii]

[00:01.43]Lay Me Down (Avicii by Avicii) - Avicii
[01:15.58]I feel weak, things get tough
[01:18.03][01:21.70][01:25.55][01:29.14][01:32.96][01:36.64][01:40.58][01:44.92][01:46.97][01:50.74][01:54.70][01:58.53][02:02.92][02:06.03][02:13.59][03:33.11][03:36.63][03:40.49][03:44.19][03:48.06][03:51.49][03:55.35][03:59.31][04:05.77][04:13.38][04:14.65][04:25.02][04:28.44]
[01:19.09]Sometimes my knees can barely hold me up
[01:22.81]I'm no fool, but it's said
[01:26.14]You gotta walk a mile 'til you're outta my head
[01:30.34][03:45.31]Come within, taste it up
[01:33.68][03:48.91]Take a little bit and baby don't you give up
[01:37.89][03:52.87]Cast your light, give a damn
[01:41.30][03:56.35]You gotta make a move and
[01:43.05][03:58.14]show me where we can stand
[01:45.74][02:00.18][04:00.30]Lay me down in darkness
[01:48.33][02:03.89][04:03.59][04:18.75]Tell me what you see
[01:52.52][02:07.58][04:07.55][04:22.58]Love is where the heart is
[01:55.90][02:11.28][04:11.27][04:25.88]Show me I'm the one,
[01:57.13][02:12.16][04:12.15][04:26.77]tell me I'm the one that you need
[01:59.16][04:14.08](Come on)
[03:30.55]We all weep, bleed the same
[03:33.91]If you get the picture,
[03:35.64]leave it outta the frame
[03:37.88]In the now, take a chance
[03:41.25]Make a mess,
[03:42.20]and don't forget that life is a dance
[04:15.25]Lay me down in darkness (yeah)
