[ti:Wake Me Up (Avicii Speed Remix)]
[ar:Avicii]
[al:Wake Me Up (Remixes) - Single]

[00:01.67]Wake Me Up (Avicii Speed Remix) - Avicii
[00:03.68][01:19.95][01:24.19][01:39.01][01:43.77][01:57.17][02:09.04][02:12.55][02:16.46][03:56.85][04:01.51][04:04.87][04:11.83][04:15.90][04:23.73][04:27.18][04:30.87][04:46.19]
[01:17.43]Feeling my way through the darkness
[01:21.23]Guided by a beating heart
[01:24.97]I can't tell where the journey will end
[01:28.98]But I know where it starts
[01:32.41]They tell me I'm too young to understand
[01:36.45]They say I'm caught up in a dream
[01:40.37]Well life will pass me by if I don't open up my eyes
[01:44.41]Well that's fine by me
[01:46.84][02:02.22][04:20.41][04:35.84]So wake me up when it's all over
[01:50.81][02:06.14][04:24.52][04:39.82]When I'm wiser and I'm older
[01:54.81][02:10.05][04:28.31][04:43.65]All this time I was finding myself
[01:58.09][02:13.44][04:31.79][04:47.07]And I didn't know I was lost
[03:51.03]I tried carrying the weight of the world
[03:54.72]But I only have two hands
[03:58.75]I hope I get the chance to travel the world
[04:02.38]And I don't have any plans
[04:06.35]I wish that I could stay forever this young
[04:10.09]Not afraid to close my eyes
[04:14.00]Life's a game made for everyone
[04:17.91]And love is a prize
