[ti:Long Road to Hell]
[ar:Audra Mae]
[al:True]
[by:ttpod]

[00:00.21]Long Road To Hell - Avicii
[00:01.20][00:53.77][01:53.01]
[00:13.48]Yeah
[00:16.37]So he goes.
[00:21.77]He went down to the crossroads.
[00:29.19]He said down
[00:32.67]And take his eyes from love.
[00:37.71]Everyone has a price child
[00:41.37]And what it cost him
[00:47.49]Woaa Bless his soul.
[01:18.31]You think you'll get away
[01:19.91]Don't be scared
[01:20.59]Of what you did to me.
[01:22.17]You walked right into his plan
[01:23.86]Run as fast as you think you can
[01:26.04]Go back from wherever you came
[01:27.55]You call the devil by any name
[01:29.67]I know now who you play
[01:31.41][02:36.72]Should've listened to what I say
[01:33.44][02:38.79]What I say what I say YEAH
[01:37.23]I don't know
[01:38.72]If I'll be coming home again
[01:43.01]Home again
[01:44.78]No I don't know if I'll be coming home.
[01:50.44]It's a long road to hell without no soul.
[02:23.11]Since when do
[02:23.73]You think your getting away
[02:25.32]No escape with that deal you made.
[02:27.42]You walked right into his plan.
[02:29.17]Run as fast as you think you can.
[02:31.17]Just go wherever you can
[02:32.90]Call the devil by any name
[02:34.82]Ah no no who do you playing
[02:42.90]Let me tell you it's a hard road ahead
[02:45.60]Without no soul.
