[ti:Shame on Me]
[ar:Avicii]
[al:True]

[00:00.54]Ok (Now start singing)
[00:02.31][00:18.02][00:19.78][00:36.90][00:57.21][01:03.40][01:04.95][01:08.66][01:11.08][01:51.18][01:55.29][01:58.84][02:02.53][02:11.63][02:15.88][02:31.44][02:36.17][02:43.78][02:47.60][02:50.48][03:19.91][03:22.97][04:08.68]
[00:10.23][02:04.52]Shame on me for loving you
[00:12.05]Can't deny that you been untrue
[00:13.95]Lie so sweet but you love to tease
[00:16.05]Put that fire out with gasoline
[00:17.71]Wohoa
[00:19.50]Yeah
[00:25.56][02:19.79]After five times,
[00:26.43][02:20.49]I was born again
[00:27.33]You can go to hell
[00:28.32]With your fucked-up friends
[00:29.08]You crazy little bitch in the first degree
[00:31.08][02:25.40]Shame on you for loving me
[00:32.89]Yeah! Woah-oh-oh! Oh-oh!
[00:56.15][02:35.13](Oh! My! My!)
[00:58.21][02:37.04]That's what I get for loving you!
[01:00.13][02:39.00](Lie! Lie! Lie!) No,
[01:02.33][02:41.17]I can't live without you!
[01:04.03][02:42.87](Why? Why? Why?)
[01:05.70][02:44.66]And all those things
[01:06.70][02:45.58]You put me through!
[01:07.90][02:46.72](Right? Right? Right?)
[01:09.52][02:48.48]So, I get my kicks without you!
[01:49.56][01:57.20][04:06.82]That's what I get for loving you
[01:53.33][02:01.05]I could not live without you
[02:06.21]But you can't deny
[02:07.06]That you've been untrue
[02:08.27]You lie so sweet
[02:09.09]But you love me deep
[02:10.24]Putting out fire with your gasoline
[02:13.16]Dot-dot-dot! Dot-Up! Heh-eh-eh!
[02:21.62]I'mma raise hell to the bitter end
[02:23.36]I'm a crazy little
[02:24.22]Bitch in the first degree
[02:27.30]Ha! Yay, yeah yeah! Uh, uh, uh!
[03:16.98]But I would leave
[03:18.47]When you would not
[03:20.45]It'll end with you, with you
[04:09.32]Shame on Me - Avicii
