[ti:Levels Radio Edit]
[ar:Avicii]
[al:Ultimate Clubland 2012]
[by:kaka]

[00:00.36]Levels Radio Edit - Avicii
[00:02.96]
[01:23.92][01:39.19]Oh sometimes
[01:27.13][01:36.34][01:42.30][01:52.31]I get a good feeling yeah
[01:31.89][01:47.18]Get a feeling that I never
[01:33.79][01:48.74]never never never had before no no
